Mss.B.Ey83
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, July 13, 1869; 8x5; Moore, T J
    Liverpool, A.L.S. 2p. Thanks for publication. Letterhead of Liverpool Free Public Library.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 24, 1869; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    Wales, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Sept. 28, 1869; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 3p. Death of his wife. Refers to Gray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Jan. 27, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Feb. 8, 1870; 8x5; Marshall, G. F. L. (George Frederick Leycester), 1843-1934
    A.L.S. 6p. Concerning birds. Refers to Gray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 20, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Marshall, G. F. L. (George Frederick Leycester), 1843-1934
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 27, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Marshall, G. F. L. (George Frederick Leycester), 1843-1934
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 1, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Brookes, John
    A.L.in 3rd.P. 2p. Concerning an analysis of Potato Manure.
  - Letter to T[homas C.] Eyton, June 2, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Gray, John Edward, 1800-1875
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning insects.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 8, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Gray, John Edward, 1800-1875
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning insects. Thanks for birds. Refers to Gray, Owen and Günther.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Sept. 21, 1870; 7x4-1/2; Sharpe, Richard Bowdler, 1847-1909
    A.L.S. 4p. Will buy his African birds. Refers to Fraser.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 8, 1870; 7x4; Sharpe, Richard Bowdler, 1847-1909
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 4, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 11, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 15, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 4, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Gray, George Robert, 1808-1872
    Eastbourne A.L.S. 1p. Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Oct. 10, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 3, 1871; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, 1871; 4-1/2x3-1/2; Gray, George Robert, 1808-1872
    [ca.]. A.L.S. 2p. Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Jan. 29, 1872; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 3, 1872; 9x7-1/2; Charlesworth, Edward
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning his difficulty of making a living stuyding natural history. Written on printed prospectus of Mr. Whincopp's collection.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 10, 1872; 8x5; Charlesworth, Edward
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning fossils.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 11, 1872; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 17, 1872; 7x4-1/2; Walden, Lord
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, June 25, 1872; 8x5; Charlesworth, Edward
    A.L.S. 8p. Concerning fossils.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 10, 1872; 8x5; Charlesworth, Edward
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, July 13, 1872; 8x5; Charlesworth, Edward
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 7, 1872; 7x4-1/2; Jardine, William, Sir, 1800-1874
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Nov. 22, 1872; 6x4; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning architecture.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, May 27, 1873; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Flower, William Henry, 1831-1899
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning a skeleton. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Thomas C. Eyton, June 2, 1873; 10x8; Royal College of Surgeons of England.
    Printed L.filled in in ms.S.: Edward Trimmer. 1p. Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, Aug. 21, 1873; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Owen, Richard, 1804-1892
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], Aug. 28, 1873; 7x4-1/2; Flower, William Henry, 1831-1899
    A.L.S. 1p. Concerning skeletons. Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 6, 1873; 10x8; Royal College of Surgeons of England.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, Oct. 9, 1873; 10x8; Zoological Society of London
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, March 20, 1874; 7x4-1/2; Garrod, A. H. (Alfred Henry), 1846-1879
    London, A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, April 2, 1874; 8x5; Gould, John, 1804-1881
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning skeletons of birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, April 6, 1874; 7x4-1/2; Waterhouse, G. R. (George Robert), 1810-1888
    A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter. Refers to Owen.
  - Sunday Morning, undated; Clipping from letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 6x4; Adams, Andrew Leith, d. 1882
    London, A.L.S. 3p. Concerning a fossil.
  - Account of tortoises., undated; 7x4-1/2; Bonaparte, Charles Lucian, 1803-1857
    D. 1p.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880
    West minister, A.L.S. 3p. Will be glad to meet him.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Buckland, Francis T. (Francis Trevelyan), 1826-1880
    Westminster A.L.S. 1p. Thanks for favor.
  - Letter to Thomas C. Eyton, undated; Darwin, Charles, 1809-1882
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Darwin, Charles, 1809-1882
    Down, Saturday evening. A.L.S. 4p. Concerning shells.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 6-1/2x4; Denny, Henry
    Wednesday afternoon A.L.S. 1p. Concerning one of his publications.
  - Letter to Hugh Cuming, undated; 7x4-1/2; Derby, Edward George Geoffrey Smith Stanley, Earl of, 1799-1869
    London. A.L.S. 2p.and add. Business.
  - Letter to the mayor of Liverpool, undated; 4-1/2x3; Derby, Edward George Geoffrey Smith Stanley, Earl of, 1799-1869
    Knowsley, Newspaper clipping. 1p. Sets up natural history museum.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Dyson, David
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Egerton, Philip de Malpas, Sir, 1806-1881
    A.L.S. 1p. Forwards shells.
  - Memorandum., undated; 3x4-1/2; Eyton, T. C. (Thomas Campbell), 1809-1880
    D. 1p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Forbes, Edward, 1815-1854
    A.L.S. 1p. Gives location of scallop beds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Forbes, Edward, 1815-1854
    A.L.S. 4p. Concerning mollusks and plants. Refers to Thomson.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Gould, John, 1804-1881
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 8x5; Gould, John, 1804-1881
    A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter. concerning birds.
  - Letter to T[homas C.] Eyton., undated; 7-1/2X4-1/2; Gray, George Robert, 1808-1872
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton]., undated; 9x7; Gray, John Edward, 1800-1875
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. Asks a favor.
  - Letter to [Hugh Cuming]., undated; 7x4-1/2; Günther, Albert C. L. G., (Albert Carl Ludwig Gotthilf), 1830-1914
    A.L.S. 3p. Friendly letter. Birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    Birmingham, A.L.S. 4p. Concerning natural history. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Houghton, William
    Birmingham, A.L.S. 8p. Concerning natural history. Asks to borrow books.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Marshall, G. F. L. (George Frederick Leycester), 1843-1934
    Saturday, 22nd. A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Marshall, G. F. L. (George Frederick Leycester), 1843-1934
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning a bird.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds. Refers to Gould.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Monday, 18. A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 10x8; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Oxford, Tuesday. A.L.S. 1p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Tuesday evening. A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7x4; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Thursday. A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds. Refers to Gould and Gray.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton., undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Concerning birds. Concerning Fraser.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    A.L.S. 2p. Borrows book. Concerning skeletons.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton., undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds. Refers to Jardine and Gould.
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton, undated; 8-1/2x7; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Hampshire. A.L.S. 4p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913
    Picadilly. A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton]., undated; 7x4-1/2; Strickland, H. E. (Hugh Edwin), 1811-1853
    A.L. 2p. Post script of a letter. Concerning birds. Is this part of the letter of April 7, 1853?
  - Letter to [Thomas C.] Eyton., undated; 7x4-1/2; Symonds, W. S. (William Samuel), 1818-1887
    A.L.S. 3p. Concerning birds, mollusks and fossils. Refers to Strickland.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 5-1/2x3-1/2; Tennent, James Emerson, Sir, 1804-1869
    Ballywalter. A.L.S. 2p. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to T[homas] C. Eyton, undated; 7x4-1/2; Wallace, Alfred Russel, 1823-1913
    A.L.S. 2p. Concerning birds. Refers to Sclater.
  - Letter to [Thomas C. Eyton], undated; 7x4-1/2; Wollaston, Thomas Vernon, 1822-1878
    Monday evening. A.L.S. 3p. Concerning shells.
  - Epitath on the tomb of Hugh Davies, undated